I'm sorry, Nico.
But now, you know the real me.
I'm Alyana Heartily Ferrer.
Dead?
How did that happen? He was...
He was still so young.
And he was perfectly healthy.
He wasn't even sick.
I can take good care
of my daughter, Roswell.
Young was still new, right?
If another Mafia took him out,
what would they
even gain from it?
Boulstridge, keep an
eye on my wife's mother.
Lerwick,
investigate the Mafia group that
Kevin Alferez joined.
Lee.
Find out who the fuck is this
so-called guardian angel of my wife.
And you, Lamperouge.
Keep an eye on Yaji.
What about me, Dong?
What am I supposed to do?
- What's that?
- Nothing.
I'll give you 15 minutes to
memorize their background.
Whoa.
15 minutes? That's so fast.
They look so cool, Dong.
I'm going to eliminate
them one by one.
Why are you showing me all this?
Why do you think?
Did the Yaji's have something
to do with Moo's death?
I'm not yet sure.
But they are the mafia,
Nico Jeisz Young was trying to join.
So even if they didn't kill him,
they are still
responsible for him.
His blood is on their hands.
That's right.
Someone has to answer
for what happened to Moo.
Tomorrow, first
thing in the morning,
you're gonna start
your real training.
Really?
This is for real now, Zeke?
Okay.
Does that mean I'll
become a Mafia too?
I'm gonna be in the Mafia?
Awesome!
You already are one.
Pew!
Pew, pew!
Psst!
This is a robbery.
Hand over your wallet.
Your wallet!
Pew, pew!
Sit down.
I need a codename.
- Eat.
- I wonder what my codename should be.
Moo.
Moo!
Hey! Hi, Moo!
Aww, so cute!
Me or the puppy?
Both.
Moo!
Moo.
Sorry Moo.
Moo?
Moo!
Hey, hey.
Are you okay?
Wife.
Zeke, I dreamed about Moo.
I still can't believe he's gone.
And...
in my dream, you were the...
you were the one who shot him.
But I know it wasn't you.
because you'd never do that.
I'm sorry, Zeke.
Don't be sorry.
I understand.
Shh, that's enough.
If you don't feel
up to training,
you should get some rest.
No, no.
I have to train. I
have to get stronger.
I have to get stronger for Moo.
So when we find out
who did this to him,
I'll be strong enough
to face them all.
Alright.
Huh.
Wow, it's still so early.
Did my school schedule change?
Or can I just go back to sleep?
If you really want to train,
you have to get up and
fix yourself in the morning.
So you can get more done.
Didn't you say you
wanted to learn everything?
Yeah, but...
Take a quick shower now,
I'll wait for you downstairs.
I love you.
I love you too.
I should've just chosen to rest.
Why'd I have to
get all dramatic?
Left.
Right, right.
Knee.
One more.
Right hook.
Left hook.
Wait.
What?
Do you still want to continue?
Can you keep going?
Yeah, I can. Just wait.
I'm doing this so I
can protect myself.
And the people I love.
Including me?
Of course, including you.
Good.
10-minute break.
Then, we'll proceed
to gun firing.
Huh?
Really?
Whoa!
Let's do it now.
I'm ready.
Relax.
Let's wait once you've
regained your energy.
Then, we'll continue.
Ow!
Quit pouting.
You look like a duck.
A duck?
Does it hurt?
Whoa!
PDA!
What the fuck do you
need, Lamperouge?
It's about Yaji, boss.
What's your update on Yaji?
Have you found
their other members?
Not yet, boss.
Yaji?
I'll let you know as soon
as Jacob updates me.
Were the Yaji's behind what
happened to Moo?
Do you know who killed him?
Not yet, Ma'am Aemie.
But I have a hunch
who Yaji's boss is.
Who?
Eiji Ferrer.
But I still don't have enough information,
so I'm not completely sure yet.
Eiji.
Eiji Ferrer?
You know him?
Zeke...
He's Caileigh's dad.
I—Impossible.
Impossible.
I told you.
You cannot trust anyone.
What's the plan, boss?
She has a daughter, huh?
Kill her.
Zeke?
What are you saying?
You're talking about
killing my friend.
And we're not even
sure he's Yaji's boss yet.
Besides, Caileigh
Ferrer is adopted.
And from what I've learned, Eiji
Ferrer and Caileigh aren't that close.
Caileigh's adopted?
Yes, Ma'am Aemie.
So killing Caileigh would
probably be pointless.
But we don't know
how much she
already knows about us.
Especially about Aemie.
Wait, hold on.
Do you even hear yourselves?
You're talking about
killing my friend!
You're going to kill my friend?
She could be pretending
to be your friend.
We don't know. She might already
be planning something against you.
So if that's what it
takes to keep you safe,
then yes.
Is that really how
you think, Zeke?
All you ever think about
is killing, killing, killing!
One of my friends just died!
And now you want
to kill another one?
How are you any different from the
heartless people who did that to Moo?
You're not laying a
finger on my friend.
And that's final.
Where's your boss?
Uh, Ms. Stonehurst, Mr. Roswell
is not picking up his cellphone.
I don't care!
Call him again!
Uh, yes, Ms. Stonehurst.
What's that woman been
feeding you, Ezekiel?
So not you.
Why?
Let's meet.
Can we do it later?
No.
Let's meet now.
Could they be the people
Auntie wanted me to meet?
Excuse me, miss.
Need someone to watch that with?
If there are still tickets left.
Look at how big
this production is.
I'm sure it's already sold out.
Leave it to me.
What?!
A-after flirting with—
Charina, you're gonna apologize?
Just play along.
Baby, you know she's the
one who flirted with me, right?
Besides, I didn't flirt with—
Roselle! I'm sorry.
Roselle?
That's Charina. Look
at you, all confused.
You have way too many girls.
Baby.
You know you're
the one I love, right?
Don't be jealous, okay?
Hey.
Pervert!
Since you keep coming
over here and acting all cute,
you might as well
buy me coffee.
But we don't even
know each other yet.
I'm Shin.
Can you treat me now?
Why are you still standing
there? Go order already!
Okay, baby.
Hello, Auntie?
Did you find the person
I asked you to tail?
Yes, but there's
this annoying guy.
Annoying?
Yeah, but...
Somehow, his nosy
ass actually helped.
What's his name?
I don't know, Auntie,
and I'm not interested.
He's so annoying.
Call me later, Auntie.
Okay, I'm gonna go
deal with that idiot first.
Okay, Mik. I'll call you later too.
Let's talk.
Were you the one
who did that to Young?
No.
I don't have the
guts to kill a man.
Age really does
matter, doesn't it?
Talking to you is
such a waste of time.
What do you mean?
Age does really matter.
You're too young to surpass me.
I'm not your enemy.
Who are you?
You guess.
I didn't plan on buying for two.
Then stop trying to act all handsome.
But I am handsome.
Wait,
why are you here anyway?
Why are
you staring at those five men?
I bet one of them is your ex.
You're probably trying to make him jealous,
that's why you pulled that stunt earlier.
And if you're gonna date someone,
at least don't pick an ugly one.
Wow, you're not
exactly a looker yourself.
What the hell?
What are those two doing here?
Why is Fiona here?
Why is she with Lionhart?
Hey, is something wrong?
Who are they? Do you know them?
Boss, Fiona and Lionhart
just met up with those five men.
Okay, follow Lionhart.
Auntie, two people
just showed up.
- A woman and a man.
- Okay, Boss.
And I think the idiot
I met knows them.
Who are they?
That idiot said
their names are
Fiona and Lionhart.
Okay, you're doing great. I'll
deposit the money into your account.
And keep following
the man you mentioned.
Huh? Where'd he go?
Shit, I didn't get his name.
Yes, Zeke.
I'll do better next time.
I just need to
rest for a bit. Wait.
Wife.
I'm sorry if you feel that I'm
not considering your feelings.
But I hope you understand
that I'm only doing
this to protect you.
Wife, please.
Listen to me.
In the Mafia world, it's
hard to trust anyone.
Not even your closest friends.
That's why I'm teaching you
not to kill, but to
protect yourself,
even against me.
This is my world.
And you were never
meant to be part of it.
I was the one who
pulled you into this mess.
And that's on me.
If anything happens to
you, it will always be my fault.
And I'll never forgive myself
if anything bad happens to you.
I understand, Zeke.
But just like you,
I'm only thinking
about the people I love.
So please,
think your decisions
through more carefully.
Okay for you.
Until proven guilty,
I won't do anything.
Promise?
Promise.
Sorry, boss. Am I interrupting?
No, Sebastian. It's okay.
Go ahead.
I'll be back.
Okay.
She has a daughter, huh?
Kill her.
Why is it like this?
Even after Zeke and I talked,
this is still how
I feel about him.
I'm still scared,
and it still hurts.
Wife.
Wife, wake up.
It's seven.
Come on.
Get up.
Wake up.
You liar!
You tricked me!
Me?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
You're a liar!
You said I'd get stronger,
but everything you taught
me just made me weaker.
It hurts.
Oh, you're laughing now?
You did that on
purpose, didn't you?
You're so mean.
Hey, hey, why are you—
Don't break my arm.
I'm telling Mom on you!
Be quiet.
Soreness.
That's what happens if you
don't have regular exercise.
But don't worry.
You'll be better
after a few days.
Like that?
There!
That feels so good.
So good.
Turn around.
Huh?
Lie face down!
Okay.
Hey!
There.
That feels so good.
It feels amazing!
Wow, Zeke! This feels so good!
Hey, Dong! You're
really good at massages!
What if you open
a massage parlor?
Right?
I know, I'll suggest a name.
What if...
Dodong's Massage Parlor?
Aha!
Oh, wait.
Or maybe...
Uncle Zeke's Massage?
Oh?
Ow!
No!
I got it, I got it!
In Dodong's Hands.
Or...
You're in good
hands with Dodong.
Right?
Are you messing with me?
No.
I'm just making suggestions.
What if...
I just give you a happy ending?
What do you think?
Happy ending?
Yeah.
You're right, Zeke!
You're right!
I deserve a happy ending.
You deserve a happy ending.
Everybody deserves
a happy ending!
Why are you laughing? I'm right.
Right?
Because it's true.
We all deserve a happy ending.
Despite everything that's
happening in our country, right?
Why are you laughing?
Get up already!
Even if there's no training,
you still have school.
Come on!
Get up!
I'll drive you.
Hey!
Hey, what about
the happy ending?
Where's the happy ending?
You're trapped with me now.
Shout,
and I'll cut your throat.
Why are you following her?
Following who?
I'll ask you again.
Why are you following
Aemie Roswell?
I'm guarding her.
Guarding?
Why?
Who are you?
Why do you care?
Your name?
Fauzia.
Arcadia.
Take a look at the blueprint.
They've already seen it too.
Are you sure the launch is
happening inside Roswell Corporation?
Yeah.
Can I have a copy of this?
I only have one copy.
I'll have two more made later.
Okay.
What are you looking at?
Thank you for
waiting, ma'am sir.
Here's your order and
please let me know if there's
anything I can get for you.
Thank you.
Are you sure no
one followed you?
I think I need to go.
Wait.
Oh, why?
Where's the freaking blueprint?
Fuck!
Weren't you just holding it?
I just set it down here.
Babe?
Babe, can we meet up today?
I can't, babe.
I'm at work.
Work?
You're just standing there.
Babe?
Hi, babe.
Hello.
Hey, let's go.
Fatima's already there.
Her breath smells like shit.
Ew.
Right?
It stinks!
Can you see me now, Moo?
Yeah.
Is this for me?
Happy Valentine's Day, Moo!
Thank you.
Oh, my God. You're so cute!
I'm really sorry, Moo.
Sorry, Moo.
Sorry.
It's okay, Moo.
Don't think about it anymore.
I don't even know why I'm crying.
Is it because I miss Moo, or
because I'm hungry?
Hey!
Oh.
My ride's here.
Where are Jacob and the others?
Hi, miss.
Looks like you're all alone here.
Huh?
Seems like your
ride's taking a while.
Ezekiel Roswell.
Do you want to...
grab a bite first?
Are you friends with Zeke?
I'm Phoenix.
And this is Cyd.
By the way, I'm—
Aemie Roswell.
Right?
Whoa.
They know me.
And Zeke too.
How nice.
How about we treat you to dinner?
Then after that,
we'll take you back.
Don't worry.
We're nice people.
Okay, but let's
make it quick, okay?
- Yeah!
- Sure.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Let's go, let's go.
Where's your car?
You don't have a car?
There's something
I wanted to tell you.
What is it?
Will you be my boyfriend?
Auntie,
those two are with a woman.
What's up with the woman?
Well, it's a little
suspicious because
they just talked to the girl here at
Stonehurst, then took her with them.
Should I follow them?
Uh, hello, hello, Auntie.
Hello.
Oh, no.
Your relationship will also end.
Babe's really something.
She really likes being babied.
Uhh.
Boss, Ma'am Aemie?
Damn you.
I should be the
one asking you that.
Where the fuck is my wife?
Sorry, boss. I don't know.
I just found her pink
keychain on the ground.
Sorry, boss.
You only have one job.
One fucking job!
And you still failed!
I could kill you!
Sorry, boss.
Fuck!
Shit!
Boss,
calm down.
Finding your wife is our priority.
Everyone!
Look for my wife!
Now!
Now! Move it!
Mr. Roswell.
We'll find her.
Damn it, my phone's dead.
Uhm.
Can I borrow your phone?
Why?
What are you going
to do with my phone?
Is this guy an idiot?
What do you think
people use phones for?
Why doesn't he know?
I just need to make a call.
My phone died.
Thank you.
Come on! Of all times,
Zeke had to be on a long call.
Thanks.
Hey!
Oh my god!
Are we playing?
Why?
You wanna play?
Sure!
Let's do it!
But,
let's add a plot twist.
Deal?
Someone dies.
Hey!
That's like those movies
where the main character dies.
I don't wanna die yet.
That would've been nice,
but that's not how this goes.
You're not dying yet.
Okay.
Here's how it works.
I'll give each of us five cards.
Whoever wins gets to
ask anything they want.
Oh, I get it.
Like truth or consequence?
Exactly!
So?
You in?
Sure, let's play!
Did you get it?
Fuck, bro.
Don't you have any faith in me?
Guess what?
It's the blueprint of
Roswell Corporation.
But what I don't get is,
how did they get a copy of this?
I don't know either, bro.
But the question is,
who'd they get it from?
Fiona?
I don't know either, bro.
Maybe we should just
take this to boss.
Bro!
What, already missing
this handsome face?
Idiot! Aemie's missing.
Boss is losing it!
Damn!
Damn right! We're
gonna feel boss's wrath
if we don't find
Aemie. So get moving!
Fuck.
Shit.
Let's go.
Where do you think she went?
I don't know either.
Whoa!
That's so unfair!
I keep losing. I don't wanna play anymore.
Sorry, rules are rules.
So, for your last question,
answer this honestly so
you can go home.
Okay, sure.
What was Roswell's
last order to his men?
These people are so weird.
First they asked about Moo.
Then it was about Mom.
And now it's about Zeke?
Wait.
Could this be a test?
Oh. Then I better answer well.
Uhh.
He told Kaizer to keep an eye on Yaji.
Then Vash was
assigned to watch Mom.
Then Sebastian was sent
to investigate a Mafia group.
Then Jacob was assigned
to the guardian angel.
Why are you laughing?
No, I'm serious.
I'm not kidding.
Yeah.
We know you're not kidding.
That's why we're taking you home.
Just show us where you live.
But, Aemie,
can you not mention
us to Roswell?
Our names.
And what we talked about.
Wow.
What do you take me for, a gossip?
Of course I won't tell him.
You're so judgmental.
But what if he asks?
We have a surprise for Mr. Roswell.
So it has to stay a secret.
- Oh!
- Secret.
A surprise? Okay, okay, okay.
I won't tell him.
Our little secret.
Just between us.
Can I take this home?
Aemie!
Boss!
I've already sent everyone out.
They're searching for her now.
Okay?
Fuck!
Hey!
Zeke, why do you have this?
I gave this to—
Who's that?
Must've followed you here.
Are you stupid?
What if Roswell finds out?
My friends at Stonehurst?
Don't you know them?
Ezekiel, I brought you some lunch.
From a very fancy restaurant.
My wife bought our lunch.
Right wife?
Uh, yes, hubby.
Allow me to present,
our artisanal
handheld beef creation.
Fast-food lang yan!
Want a bite?
I want nothing...
but your husband.
And sooner or later...
he will be mine.
So keep that in mind,
Aemie.